# JOHN MWAURA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ENGINEER
/IT/PROCUREMENT AND SUPPLY CHAIN
MANAGEMENT OFFICER

#### CONTACT

+254115282069/+254755564686

https://mwaurawebnextcv.vercel.app

🛇 Kenya, Nairobi

https://github.com/Jonnie-bot

https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-/

#### SKILLS

Negotiation Communication Skills

Problem Solving

Networking

Web Development

Mobile Development

Computer

#### EDUCATION

## **Computer Science**

St. Pauls University

2019-2021

Diploma In Computer Science

# Supply and Procurement Management

# **Mount Kenya University**

2012-2017

Diploma In Supply and Procurement Management.

#### **Computer Science**

#### **Zetech University**

2023-Continue
Bachelors In Computer
Science

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced Procurement Officer, Supply Chain Officer, Customer Representative and Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Customer services, Logistics, Supply Chain and Tech industry. Skilled in Coding, Management and Customer Service. Strong professional with a diploma in Purchasing and Supplies focused in Purchasing, Procurement/Acquisitions and Supply CHain Management from Mount Kenya University as well as diploma in Computer Science focused in Web and Mobile that is Fullstack Development from St. Paul University, Kenya.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Developer**

Freelance

2022-To Date

- Web App Development Next Js.
- Mobile App Development using Expo React Native.
- Backend Development Node Js, Nest Js.

## **Supply Chain**

Juan Bass Enterprise LTD

2019-2022

- Procure ICT equipments for companies at the lowest price possible.
- Supply ICT equipments and Building equipments.
- Ensure quality and quantity are at par.
- Negotiate with suppliers.

#### **Buyer**

Modenta Company Limited

2019-2022

- Consulting in identifying purchasing needs.
- Negotiating with suppliers.
- Inventory Management.

### Logistics

National Aviation Services, Kuwait

2017-2018

• Handle Customers luggage.

# JOHN MWAURA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ENGINEER
/IT/PROCUREMENT AND SUPPLY CHAIN
MANAGEMENT OFFICER

#### REFERENCE

# Mary Muthangia ☐ CPF: Manager ☐ +254728965300 ☑ info.@cpf.or.ke Mr. Kenneth Mwangi ☐ Head of Supply Chain Management: Ministry of Interior and Coordination of National Government ☐ +254722573683

# Miss. Petwa N. Malaba

- Tutorial Fellow : The Technical University of Kenya
- +254720548465
- Malabapetwa@gmail.com

#### - - - - -

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

# **Supply Chain Officer**

Gewino Enterprises Ltd

2017-2017

- Planning delivery timetables
- Ensuring stores have enough stock,
- Monitoring stock levels
- Overseeing the arrival of shipments.

#### **Procurement Intern**

Ministry of Interior and Coordination of National 2016-2016 Government

- Stock taking and stock control.
- Market survey for items to be procured by the department.
- Assisting in processing suppliers payments.
- Assisting in receiving and issuance of stores against approved requisitions.
- Assisting in preparation of quotations of goods and service.
- Assisting in preparing of Agendas and minutes for procurement committee meetings.

#### **Supply Chain Officer**

Gewino Enterprises Ltd

2014-2016

- Preparation of supply orders.
- Stock Management, Management of supplies.
- Budget preparation and record keeping

#### **Data Entry**

CPF 2012-2013

- Scanned documents.
- Entered documents data into the computer.